[upbeat ukulele music]
[欢快的尤克里里音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[baby cooing]
[婴儿咕咕声]
- Oh!
- [laughing]
- 哦！
- [笑]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
I can't see!
我看不见！
[tires screech, both screaming]
[轮胎发出刺耳的声音，两人都尖叫]
Mama! Papa! No!
妈妈！爸爸！不！
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
both: Whoa!
两人：哇！
[tires squeal, both screaming]
[轮胎发出尖叫声，两人都尖叫]
Bikini Bottom's long-awaited
dynamite factory
比基尼泳裤期待已久
炸药厂
is now open!
- Look out!
现已开放！
- 小心！
Huh?
啊？
both: Whoa!
两人：哇！
Oh, phew.
哦，唷。
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
Hey, Mrs. Puff, I can see
your house from up here.
从这里看你的房子。
Huh?
啊？
[quirky music]
[古怪的音乐]
[sighs]
[叹气]
Look at that.
You saved me a commute.
看看那个。
你节省了我的通勤时间。
Just let yourself out.
就让自己出去吧。
Well, if you're sure...
好吧，如果你确定...
See you tomorrow, Mrs. Puff!
明天见，普芙女士！
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
Maybe he really is unteachable.
也许他真的是不可教的。
I give up.
我放弃。
No, Puff, not yet.
不，普夫，还没有。
You're a driving instructor!
你是一名驾驶教练！
Instructing that boy
is your duty.
教导那个男孩
是你的职责。
You just need a little guidance.
你只需要一点指导。
[calm music]
[平静的音乐]
[phone ringing, vibrating]
[电话铃声、振动]
The universe greets you.
宇宙向你问好。
Allow me to guide
your celestial vessel.
请允许我指导
你的天船。
SpongeBob...
海绵宝宝...
driving...
驾驶...
me...
我...
crazy!
疯狂的！
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
Oh, Mrs. Puff.
哦，帕夫夫人。
Perhaps it would help
也许会有帮助
if you find a way to be
with SpongeBob
如果你找到办法
与海绵宝宝
without being
with SpongeBob, hmm?
没有存在
和海绵宝宝一起，嗯？
Okay.
好的。
Feel free to annoy me
for money again soon.
随意惹恼我
很快又要钱了。
Goodbye.
再见。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grunts]
[咕哝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Ah...
啊...
Less stress.
[bell dings]
压力较小。
[铃声]
Being with SpongeBob
without being with SpongeBob.
和海绵宝宝在一起
没有和海绵宝宝在一起。
[groans]
But how?
[呻吟]
但如何呢？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[breathes deeply]
[深呼吸]
[harmonious music plays]
Huh?
[和谐的音乐响起]
啊？
Where is that music coming from?
那音乐是从哪里来的？
A submarine?
潜艇？
That gives me an idea.
这给了我一个想法。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[music continues]
[音乐继续]
♪ ♪
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
I knew it!
我就知道！
Where there are sailors,
there are always potatoes.
有水手的地方，
总是有土豆。
♪ ♪
[mysterious music]
[神秘的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Huh?
Qu'est-ce que c'est?
啊？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
There.
That should do it.
那里。
应该可以做到这一点。
- ♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
- Huh?
- ♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
- 啊？
Gah!
- ♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
嘎！
- ♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
[grunts]
D'oy!
[咕哝]
哎哟！
Oh, Mrs. Puff!
哦，帕夫夫人！
It's been so long!
Did you miss me?
已经过去这么久了！
你想念我吗？
Oh, yes, SpongeBob.
哦，是的，海绵宝宝。
I missed you so much.
我非常想念你。
It's so good to see you...
很高兴见到你...
from here.
从这里。
Ooh! Did you get a new hat?
哦！你买新帽子了吗？
It really brings out
all your eyes.
它确实带出了
你所有的眼睛。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
[laughs]
[笑]
All right...
好的...
Time to focus on the road,
my excellent little noodle.
是时候把注意力集中在路上了
我优秀的小面条。
Oh! I must live up
to your noodle-spectations!
哦！我必须活下去
满足您的面条期望！
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
How was that?
怎么样？
That was very good.
那很好。
Okay, take a right here.
好的，在这里右转。
Now keep going right.
现在继续向右走。
Feels right to me!
[laughs]
我觉得很对！
[笑]
Ah, yes, it does.
啊，是的，确实如此。
Now I can catch up
on my stories.
现在我可以赶上
关于我的故事。
Oh, Dwayne.
哦，德韦恩。
The only thing
I've ever loved...
唯一的一件事
我曾经爱过...
[bell rings]
Is a skull-cracking smackdown!
[铃声响起]
是一记惊天动地的重击！
[grunts]
[cheering]
[咕哝]
[欢呼]
That's right!
这是正确的！
[static whirs]
- Keep going right?
[静电呼呼声]
- 继续吧？
All right.
Um, yeah.
好的。
嗯，是的。
Sure, SpongeBob.
当然，海绵宝宝。
Boy, I really feel like
I'm getting the hang
男孩，我真的觉得
我正在掌握窍门
of this turning-right thing.
这个右转的事情。
Hey, this is the longest I've
ever driven without crashing.
嘿嘿，这是我最长的一次了
曾经开车没有撞车过。
[grunts]
Huh?
[咕哝]
啊？
Oh.
There's none left.
哦。
没有了。
[static whirs]
Left.
[静电呼呼声]
左。
Left?
But I'm still working on right.
左边？
但我仍然在努力。
Do you really think I'm ready?
你真的认为我准备好了吗？
[static whirs]
- Yeah!
[静态呼呼声]
- 是啊！
Oh, okay, if you think so.
哦，好吧，如果你这么认为的话。
[tires squealing, horn blares]
[轮胎尖叫声、喇叭声]
Oh!
[chuckles]
哦！
[笑声]
Sorry about that.
对此感到抱歉。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[tires squeal]
- Whoa!
[轮胎吱吱声]
- 哇！
Huh.
呵呵。
Some people will do anything
to use the carpool lane.
有些人什么都会做
使用拼车车道。
Huh?
Uh-oh.
啊？
呃哦。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[popcorn popping]
[爆米花爆开]
[microwave beeps]
[微波炉嘟嘟声]
[grunting and cheering on TV]
[电视上的咕哝声和欢呼声]
[horn honks]
[按喇叭]
Oh, SpongeBob?
哦，海绵宝宝？
Your driving is immaculate.
你的驾驶完美无瑕。
Just keep turning right.
继续右转即可。
Oh, I'm great at that.
哦，我很擅长。
[all giggling]
[大家咯咯地笑]
[tires squealing, all screaming]
[轮胎吱吱作响，所有人都在尖叫]
Wow!
哇！
Whoa!
[static whirs]
哇！
[静态呼呼声]
Keep that righty nice
and tight-y.
保持右手良好
和紧y。
Tightening my rightening.
收紧我的矫正。
[alarm ringing]
[警报响起]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
This is the most fulfilling day
这是最充实的一天
I've ever had as a teacher.
我曾经当过老师。
Mmm.
[chokes]
嗯。
[窒息]
[stoplight dings] Bleh!
[红绿灯叮当声]天啊！
[choking and coughing]
- Uh-oh.
[窒息和咳嗽]
- 呃哦。
Swallowed a bug, huh?
[choking and coughing]
吞了一只虫子吧？
[窒息和咳嗽]
Attention all units...
各单位注意...
major traffic violations
in progress.
重大交通违法行为
正在进行中。
- [gasps]
- Please pursue
- [喘气]
- 请追寻
as fast as possible.
尽快。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
[gasps]
[喘气]
[siren wailing]
[警笛哀号]
This must be an advanced lesson.
这一定是一堂进阶课。
[tires squeal, sirens wailing]
- Huh?
[轮胎尖叫，警报器鸣响]
- 啊？
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[siren wailing]
[警笛哀号]
Hey, that's him...
the jerk with the spud!
嘿嘿，就是他……
那个拿着马铃薯的混蛋！
Let's get him, boys!
让我们抓住他吧，孩子们！
Ooh!
[siren wailing]
哦！
[警笛哀号]
[all growling]
[panting]
[全都咆哮]
[气喘吁吁]
[siren wailing, tires squealing]
[警笛鸣响，轮胎尖叫]
both: Ah!
两人：啊！
This historic dynamite factory
这座历史悠久的炸药工厂
has been open for one
entire day with no accidents.
已开放 1 个
一整天没有发生任何事故。
Isn't that amazing?
[siren wailing]
这不是很神奇吗？
[警笛哀号]
Huh?
啊？
[siren wailing]
[警笛哀号]
[static whirs]
- Breaker, breaker, Cabin Boy.
[静电呼呼声]
- 破坏者，破坏者，机舱男孩。
Hard to port.
- Oh, a 10-4, Mrs. Puff!
难以移植。
- 哦，10-4，普夫夫人！
[tires squeal]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
I'm gettin' too old for this.
我已经太老了，不适合做这个了。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[climactic jazz music]
[高潮爵士乐]
[grunting and screaming]
[咕哝和尖叫]
We interrupt
"Headlocks and Heartbreaks"
我们打断
“头锁和心碎”
with an emergency news bulletin.
带有紧急新闻公告。
High-speed sponge
terrorizes Bikini Bottom
高速海绵
恐吓比基尼泳裤
with potato prisoner...
和土豆囚犯...
last seen pursued by
band of bandit bikers
最后一次见到的人是
一群强盗骑自行车的人
along Kraken Avenue.
沿着 Kraken 大道。
Who knows where
he may strike next?
谁知道在哪里
他可能会下一个攻击？
Wha...
世界卫生大会...
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
My leg!
我的腿！
♪ ♪
♪♪
Uh, SpongeBob?
呃，海绵宝宝？
Gah! Hello?
嘎！你好？
Hello?
你好？
Oh, Neptune.
哦，海王星。
Enough of this leisure wig.
这种休闲假发够了。
Time for the pursuit wig!
是时候追求假发了！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[siren wailing]
[警笛哀号]
I'm a driving instructor,
我是一名驾驶教练
and I'm commandeering
this vehicle!
我正在指挥
这辆车！
I can dig it, mohawk mama.
我可以挖掘它，莫霍克妈妈。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[tire squeals, siren wailing]
[轮胎尖叫声，警报器哀号]
[tires screech]
[轮胎尖叫声]
[wailing continues]
[哀号继续]
[screams]
Turn around!
[尖叫声]
转身！
Ooh, whatever you say!
呵呵，随你怎么说吧！
Whoa!
哇！
[laughing]
[笑]
Phew.
唷。
[all growling]
[全都咆哮]
Oh, dear.
哦亲爱的。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[gasps]
Mrs. Puff!
[喘气]
泡芙太太！
You've been mashed!
你已经被砸烂了！
[cries]
[哭声]
Ahem.
咳咳。
Huh?
She's alive!
啊？
她还活着！
Oh, you sure are resilient,
Mrs. Puff.
哦，你确实很有韧性，
泡芙女士。
From now on, SpongeBob,
I'll uphold my duty
从现在起，海绵宝宝，
我会恪守我的职责
as your driving instructor
to keep you safe on the road.
作为您的驾驶教练
确保您在路上安全。
Mm.
毫米。
[grunts]
[all grumbling]
[咕哝]
[大家都在抱怨]
[hard rock music]
[硬摇滚音乐]
[gasps]
Wait a minute!
[喘气]
等一下！
You're Puff the Tuff!
你就是凝灰岩！
Will you sign my cast?
你愿意签下我的演员阵容吗？
- Oh.
- I love you!
- 哦。
- 我爱你！
- [laughing]
- What a legend!
- [笑]
- 多么传奇啊！
Oh, hi, boys.
哦，嗨，孩子们。
[sirens wailing]
[警笛哀嚎]
Looks like you got things
under control here.
看来你有东西
在这里受到控制。
Let's scram!
我们滚吧！
[sighs]
I know the drill.
[叹气]
我知道演习。
[calypso instrumental]
[calypso 乐器]
♪ ♪
♪♪
So...
所以...
what are you in for?
你来干什么？
[sighs]
[叹气]